[{"answer": "I think it's at the top because I think, you know, television forever was, you know, consumed with creating a lead charter who would be, you know, likable and I think he made him -- he made this incredibly scary guy, who in many ways, extremely likable at the same time.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "The charter Tony Soprano in the lexicon of television?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "He was -- he was in a jovial mood, Piers.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "What kind of shape was he in there?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I would agree completely with that.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "Well, I was shocked.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "But what is your reaction?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, it will be right up there.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "No, not Vegas.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "You mean like Vegas?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "No, no straight jackets.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "What, you mean like a hospital with the padded rooms and the straight jackets?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "Yes, definitely, Piers.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What are you picking up there?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, at that time -- this -- we worked together a long time ago, and he was -- it's funny because he was just beginning -- when I worked with James, \"The Sopranos\" had not yet aired, so nobody knew what it was.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "Were you aware, were the cast aware of any health issues?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Again, I can't speak for everyone else, but that was certainly the impression I got.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Is that pretty much, Kevin, how all the cast viewed him?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I got the script and I remember reading it and I was laughing out loud.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "How did Tony Soprano come into your life and into ours?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "You know, suave, good looking Mafioso guy.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, I'm shocked and I'm, you know, really incredibly sad like everybody else.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "What is your reaction to his very sad, untimely death today?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "He is very powerful.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "He didn't seem very fit, and it's probably -- don't want to speculate about what happened to him but in terms of his capacity to do these kind of roles, you as a viewer, what did you -- what did you make of his power as a figure, physically and mentally?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Quite brooding, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "He was.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "Jeffrey, we're talking a little bit about \"The Sopranos\" but he was also a great movie actor, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "I think he was taken aback himself by the scale of fame that came with the role and he really, I think, always found that a little awkward to deal with.", "docId": "130619pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "Why aren't you interested in the guy that's driving the car?", "qSentId": 511}]